MUTIJIMA BRILLANT

PROFESSIONAL DRIVER

Kimironko, Kigali 10788884646 I mutijimab@gmail.com

Career Summary

A well presented, hardworking and efficient young person, Brilliant has clean driving licenses (B, C, E) and is comfortable going on long road trips. In addition to his driver licenses, Brilliant has experience in vehicle safety and road weight capacities and owns two degree in Automotive mechanic and automotive electricity. He can remain focused for long periods of time and will always do his best to ensure a company achieves its service guarantees.

Academic Qualifications

- Jan 2014- Oct 2014: Certificate in Automotive Mechanics, Automotive electricity, Driving of trucks & Driving license of class "C" and "E", Kavumu Training Center, Nyanza
- 2009-2011: "A" level certificate, Lycee de Nyanza
- 2006-2008: "O'" level certificate, Lycee de Kicukiro APADE,

Work Experience

January 2015 - Now: Self-employed

- Car repair
- Driver on-demand

Oct 2014 – Dec 2014: Professional internship at Umusanzu Garage, Butare

Driving skills acquired whilst working

- Knowledge of driving Cars, Truck
- Car Repair: RAV4, Toyotas (Hiace, Helix, Carina, Corolla, Isuzu and Benz)
- Good geographical knowledge of the local and national road network
- Able to deliver & transport goods to local or national locations
- Secure Delivering good to schedule on time

Key Skills

Key competencies

- Safe Driving
- Customer Service
- Vehicle Safety checks
- Road traffic Law
- Willing to work overtime/shifts/including days, nights, weekend and holiday periods.

Personal skills

- Polite, friendly and have a professional appearance
- Prepared to work flexible hours to meet customer needs
- Multilingual, accurate and reliable

Language and Computer Skills

- English, French, Kinyarwanda
- Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint (Presentations)

Hobbies and interest

- Motor mechanics and trucks
- Music, soccer and movies

References

- Dr. RUGWIZANGOGA Eugene Medical Surgeon, TechnicalAdvisor, Expert Health andSafety , JPIEGO Rwanda 0788872532 | eugenrug@yahoo.fr
- Mr. GAPARAYI Guy
 OwnerofUmusanzu Garage, Butare
 0788500405
 umusanzugarage@yahoo.fr